www.TashaSalgado.design | Latashasalgado@gmail.com | 510.798.6442 | Fort Worth, Tx

about

As a designer, I combine creative and usability viewpoints that result in real-world solutions for Web and Mobile applications.

My user-centered process aids in providing a compelling user experience to improve brand loyalty, customer retention and seamless experiences for users.

projects

PUSH | iOS Prototype

- Designed a simple solution for cloud storage users who need extra security and easier organizing options.
- This app features digital security codes for file sharing and folder/categories only for organizing.
- Figma, Invision, Usability Hub Invision Prototype: https://invis.io/4YPSV8KQDWM

education

Bloc | 2018-2019 UX UI Design & Front-End Development Apprenticeship

Texas Woman's University | 2018-2019 BS Sociology

skills

User Research
Persona Creation
Interviews & Surveys
Card Sorting
User-centered Design
Sketching
Wireframing
Protoyping
Competative Analysis
User Stories
User Flows
Usability Testing
User Interface Design
HTML & CSS

experience

UX Design Apprenticeship Bloc, Remote

6/2018- Present

- Developed fundamental design skills with the guidance of seasoned mentors
- Designed web applications using the full UX process, Visual Design and Frontend Development for projects

Real Estate Agent

2/2017 - 9/ 2017

Coldwell Banker & First Class RE

- Demonstrated excellent negotiating skills as well as attention to detail and clients' needs resulting in 100 percent customer satisfaction.
- Successfully guided first time homebuyers and renters through the rental and purchase process of several properties.

Virtual Assistant

4/2012 - 11/2017

Freelancer & Fancy Hands, Remote

- Successfully established a client purging system resulting in increased revenue for several businesses
- Developed strong business skills, profitability knowledge, personnel & staff training, and marketing methods via Fortune Management seminars.